Jeffrey Huynh

jeffreyhuynh0@gmail.com | 778-709-2263 | 5280 Inverness St., Vancouver, BC

Profile

Software Developer with 2+ years of professional experience in program design and development. As a project lead software developer and designer, I have a strong background in communication, technical knowledge, and working with a team. Delivers products under pressure while adhering to strict deadlines and procedures.

Education

Diploma in Computer Science - British Columbia Institute of Technology **Bachelor's Degree in Electrical Engineering** - University of British Columbia

2018 - Present 2011 - 2015

Relevant Coursework: Object-Oriented Programming (C++, Java, C#, Python), Procedural Programming (C), Relational Databases (SQL), Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API), Algorithm Analysis, Data Structures

Professional Work Experience

Software Developer

Reva Solutions - Vancouver, BC

May 2019 – August 2020

Skills Developed: Object-oriented design and implementation, C#, .NET, VBA, Project Management, Git Control

- Proposed design documents capturing the architecture of the software solution leading to client approval of the proposed system and contract containing the scope of work
- Separated the program into 5 modularized components, implemented C# .NET code that captured each aspect of the solution with separate tests for each module and efficient turnaround of the system
- Designed and executed 15+ unit tests on each module that thoroughly examined its functionality
- Organized 3 scrum meetings per week to discuss open bugs or requests in the implemented solution which resulted in a 2-week sprint turnaround for the development team

Test Engineer II

Gaming Laboratories International, LLC - Burnaby, BC

October 2015 – August 2018

Skills Developed: VBA, Unit Test Creation and Design, Communication, Team Management

- Proposed test plans approved by clients to process large volumes of testing resulting in efficient testing of the system and client satisfaction
- Tested and certified 2+ products per week including casino machines and raffle systems
- Communicated any compliance issue with the product to the client resulting in efficient project turnaround

Personal Projects

Web Developer

September 2020 - Present

Skills Developed: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

- Presented wireframes to the client for their consideration and approval of the design
- Implemented bootstrap.js, html, and css together to form a user-facing front-end website
- Currently hosted at http://www.galpinplumbing.ca/

Certification